<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111</link>
        <description></description>
        <generator>Gutenberg</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <atom:link href="http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
            <item>
                <title>Benchmarking &amp; Comparing Static Site Generators: Gutenberg versus Hugo</title>
                <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;gutenberg-vs-hugo&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;gutenberg-vs-hugo&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;As of this post, this blog is now powered by the static site generator
&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.getgutenberg.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Gutenberg&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; instead of &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;gohugo.io&quot;&gt;hugo&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
I was pretty happy about Hugo and don&#x27;t have much bad to say about it, but
I&#x27;m even happier with Gutenberg.  This post provides an in-depth comparison
between the two on five dimensions (speed, template syntax, features,
documentation&#x2F;support, and hackability) and explains why I decided to switch.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;speed&quot;&gt;Speed&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some sense, this is the least important of the five metrics—both Hugo and
Gutenberg are fast.  Really fast.  So fast that, at least with small sites,
you&#x27;ll likely never have a noticeable wait when using either program.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I&#x27;m still starting with speed because Hugo&#x27;s tagline has always been
that it&#x27;s &amp;quot;the world&#x27;s fastest framework for building static sites&amp;quot;, and I
really wanted to know if that&#x27;s actually the case.  Hugo is constantly
bragging about it&#x27;s speed, but Gutenberg is built in Rust which—at least to
hear the Rust partisans tell it—should give it a definite speed edge.  So,
who is the ultimate speed champion?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Hexo Review</title>
                <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 16:57:52 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hexo-review&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hexo-review&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;As I&#x27;ve &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.codesections.com&#x2F;blog&#x2F;why-static-site-generators-are-great&#x2F;&quot;&gt;written about&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; a &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.codesections.com&#x2F;blog&#x2F;greatness-of-static-site-generators-ii&#x2F;&quot;&gt;couple of times&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
already, I think static site generators are pretty great.  But that
still leaves picking the right static site generator.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I&#x27;ve mentioned before, this site is built with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;gohugo.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Hugo&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, and I&#x27;m currently very happy with the setup.  However,
I didn&#x27;t start with Hugo.  My first experience with a static site
generator was actually with &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;hexo.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Hexo&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;—a static site
generator that I wanted to love but found that I just could not.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post is all about what drew me to Hexo in the first place.  And
then, part two of this review, I&#x27;ll get into what ultimately pushed
me away from it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Just How Secure Is pass-gen?</title>
                <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 17:44:45 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;how-secure-is-pass-gen&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;how-secure-is-pass-gen&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day, I posted on Mastodon that &lt;a href=&quot;www.gitlab.com&#x2F;codesections&#x2F;pas-gen&quot;&gt;pass-gen&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; (my new passphrase generator written in pure bash and designed to follow the Unix philosophy) has achieved 100 bits of entropy with default settings and is now 128 times as secure as when it first launched.
But how secure is 100 bits of entropy, really?  And how do you even go about
measuring the security of a passphrase generator, really?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;attack-vectors&quot;&gt;Attack Vectors&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security of a given password depends entirely on the method used to
attack that password.  As xkcd &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;xkcd.com&#x2F;538&#x2F;&quot;&gt;famously pointed out&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, basically all passwords are weak against physical attacks:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;blog&#x2F;how-secure-is-pass-gen&#x2F;security.png&quot; alt=&quot;xkcd 538&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But let&#x27;s set aside the $5-wrench attack for the moment, and dive into the crypto-nerd&#x27;s imagined attack.  Just what would it take to actually crack
the sort of password that pass-gen creates?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Image Compression for Website Speed: Turning it up to 11</title>
                <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 16:38:54 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;image-compression-for-website-speed&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;image-compression-for-website-speed&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A few months ago, I got very into maximizing the speed of my website.  I feel
pretty good about what I accomplished:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;blog&#x2F;image-compression-for-website-speed&#x2F;pingdom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;100% score from Pingdom tools&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I actually prefer the results from &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.webpagetest.org&#x2F;result&#x2F;180612_B9_3853bf53a2703c0582863edfd1f34791&#x2F;&quot;&gt;webpagetest.org&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, and not just because it show my site as loading even faster.  It&#x27;s open-source and seems to have a better methodology.  But it doesn&#x27;t generate as pretty a picture, so I went with the Pingdom screenshot above.)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My home page loads in well under a second, and transfers only 2.4kb of data.  All of the pages in my site loaded their above-the-fold content without any blocking scripts or external CSS.  Plus, my site is served of of Netlify&#x27;s global CDN, so it attains basically the same speed for visitors from anywhere in the world.  I was generally satisfied with that result, and stopped thinking much about my site speed.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, today, I realized that I&#x27;d let things slip a bit; I&#x27;d uploaded a few
images without giving any thought to compression, and a couple of pages were
much larger—and therefore slower—than they had any right to be.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I decided to fix that.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>My (Paranoid) Git Setup</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 07:55:24 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;my-git-setup&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;my-git-setup&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Until recently, I had a very simple git workflow: I worked in a local repository, and then pushed my changes to a single remote, which lived at GitHub.  In the case of the &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.gitlab.com&#x2F;codesections&#x2F;codesections-website&quot;&gt;code for this site&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, pushing to GitHub would automatically trigger a rebuild of the website and publish the changes live to the Internet. (Thanks, &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.netlify.com&quot;&gt;Netlify&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;!)&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This setup had the virtue of simplicity, but it had three important drawbacks:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I had no backups of any changes I&#x27;d made but not published.  For example, if I had a draft blog post, it lived &lt;em&gt;only&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; on my laptop, and thus could easily be lost.  This isn&#x27;t &lt;em&gt;that&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; big of a deal with my current workflow—unlike some &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;fosstodon.org&#x2F;@h4ck3r9&#x2F;100174544939337521&quot;&gt;some&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; bloggers, I don&#x27;t tend to keep a ton of posts as drafts.  Still, though, I&#x27;d like to not lose what I do have, and I always might keep more drafts in the future.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was relying heavily on GitHub to publish updates to my site.  If GitHub were down or locked me out of my account or something, I would have no &lt;em&gt;easy&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; way to make posts to my blog.  I could migrate to a different git host or manually update Netlify, but it wouldn&#x27;t be seamless.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I had only one backup of the site, and that was on GitHub.  If anything happen to my computer, I&#x27;d be 100% relying on GitHub for all of my site content.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, over the past week, I decided to fix all of these issues.  With my new setup, I have:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A git server on a Raspberry Pi on my home LAN.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A git server on a cheep shared host.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A GitHub-hosted repository.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A GitLab-hosted repository.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Announcing pass-gen</title>
                <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 16:44:57 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;announcing-pass-gen&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;announcing-pass-gen&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.codesections.com&#x2F;blog&#x2F;fixing-the-one-problem-with-password-managers&#x2F;&quot;&gt;last time&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, I think many password managers have a serious flaw: they don&#x27;t have a way for you to generate a secure, memorable passphrase.  That means that, if you ever have to type your password in, you&#x27;re stuck typing in something like &lt;code&gt;{!]&amp;amp;Sk)r&amp;quot;ss|$K40:]PP&#x27;&#x27;3k-&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;—and nobody wants to type &lt;code&gt;{!]&amp;amp;Sk)r&amp;quot;ss|$K40:]PP&#x27;&#x27;3k-&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also said that I&#x27;ve been using &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.bartbusschots.ie&#x2F;s&#x2F;publications&#x2F;software&#x2F;xkpasswd&#x2F;&quot;&gt;hsxkpasswd&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; to solve that issue and generate usable passphrases.  I like hsxkpasswd a lot, but there&#x27;s one thing I hate about it—it&#x27;s written in Perl.  It&#x27;s the only Perl program I have on my current computer, and it feels really burdensome to install an entire programming language just to generate a simple passphrase.  So, after being bugged by that, I finally decided to do something about it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#x27;ve written pass-gen, a pure bash password generator.  I just used it to generate a password, and I got &lt;code&gt;UPTURNED!&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;​&lt;code&gt;gone!&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;​&lt;code&gt;DASH!&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;​&lt;code&gt;renewable!&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;​&lt;code&gt;GUIDE!&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;​&lt;code&gt;joystick!524&lt;&#x2F;code&gt;—hopefully much easier to type.  I had several goals for pass-gen:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>This Website</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 13:42:25 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;projects&#x2F;codesections-website&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;projects&#x2F;codesections-website&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The website you&#x27;re reading right now!  I tried to do things a bit differently with this website.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In building this website, I had three main goals.  I wanted the site to:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;have understandable source code,&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;be self-sufficient, and&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;be the &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;hackernoon.com&#x2F;10-things-i-learned-making-the-fastest-site-in-the-world-18a0e1cdf4a7&quot;&gt;fastest site in the world&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
  &lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
Here is my analysis of how well I managed to meet these goals.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Reg Experiment</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 13:39:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;projects&#x2F;regular-expression-project&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;projects&#x2F;regular-expression-project&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Live &lt;a href=&quot;&#x2F;projects&#x2F;reg-exp&#x2F;&quot;&gt;demo avalible here&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A clone of &lt;a class=&quot;link&quot; href=&quot;http:&#x2F;&#x2F;regexmatch.herokuapp.com&#x2F;#&#x2F;&quot;&gt;RegExceptional&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, a HackReactor final project that consists of a matching game to help teach regular expressions.  My goal is to show that we can get exactly the same functionality without any frameworks and that the resulting site will not only look nearly identical, but will also load less data and do so faster.  The clone I built reduces the initial data transfer by 99.83%, and cuts the page load time from 600ms to right around 100ms, which I&#x27;m prepared to score as a victory.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Fixing the One Problem With Password Managers</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 11:43:27 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;fixing-the-one-problem-with-password-managers&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;fixing-the-one-problem-with-password-managers&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently tweaked the way I use my password manager, and it&#x27;s already
saved me considerable frustration.  Not only that, it&#x27;s also brought my
usage more in line with the Unix philosophy of using tools that do only
one thing, and do it well—and illustrated, once again, why that philosophy
is so great.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post explains my tweak, and how you can apply it.  But first, some
background.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Greatness of Static Site Generators, Part II</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 11:40:46 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;greatness-of-static-site-generators-ii&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;greatness-of-static-site-generators-ii&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&quot;&#x2F;blog&#x2F;why-static-site-generators-are-great&#x2F;&quot;&gt;last post&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, we talked about the history of website hosting and the rise of dynamic websites powered by PHP.  Now, we’re going to turn to more recent history and see how content delivery networks have changed the nature of the modern web.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;content-delivery-networks-and-the-global-mobile-web&quot;&gt;Content Delivery Networks and the Global, Mobile Web&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest advantages of the Internet is how global it is—if your site is hosted in Atlanta, it might get visitors from down the block, but it just as easily might get visitors from New York, or London, or Tokyo.  And that’s pretty incredible.  But it also raises a fundamental problem:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Why Static Site Generators Are Great</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 11:37:56 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;why-static-site-generators-are-great&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;why-static-site-generators-are-great&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;What makes static site generators so great?  And what is a static site generator, anyway?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To answer that, let’s take a step back and think about how a website works.  Skipping over some (interesting and important!) details not relevant here, to display a website all you need to do is to send visitors of the website an HTML document.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an example, take this stripped-down version of the current &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.codesections.com&quot;&gt;CodeSections&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; homepage.  To keep things simple, I’ve striped out all the CSS and the parts of the HTML related to how the page would look, which leaves us with just the basic HTML.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Recursive Learning</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 11:32:38 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;recursive-learning&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;recursive-learning&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s an interestingly recursive nature to learning programing. As part of my ongoing project to build my programing skills to a higher level, I would like to learn Node and modern JavaScript frameworks&#x2F;libraries like React and Redux.  So, that’s my starting point: What do I need to do to learn these new technologies?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except that conventional wisdom holds (and I agree) that it makes more sense to become very comfortable with vanilla JavaScript before jumping to a framework.  This makes a lot of sense, actually: A framework is a powerful tool, but at the end of the day it is compiling down to JavaScript—if I don’t understand the strengths and weaknesses of JavaScript, I won’t understand the problems that these frameworks were built to solve or the trade-offs they make.  And I won’t be able to learn them nearly as well.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I’m off to learn vanilla JavaScript.  Time to read books like Crockford’s &lt;em&gt;JavaScript: The Good Parts&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Eloquent JavaScript&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except …&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Hello World! (And past writing)</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 11:31:03 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hello-world&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;blog&#x2F;hello-world&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome!  Don’t you just love that new-blog smell?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is my new home for technical topics, book reviews, whatever else
catches my attention.  I firmly believe that web developers should have their
own digital space, one that they build, control, and fully understand.  For
me, this site is that space.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;colophon&quot;&gt;Colophon&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of this writing, this site is built using &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;gohugo.io&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Hugo&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, the
leading static site generator.  It uses a self-written theme and the source
code lives in a publicly available &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;dsock&#x2F;codesections&quot;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; [EDIT: Now a &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;gitlab.com&#x2F;codesections&#x2F;codesections-website&quot;&gt;GitLab repository&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;].  If you’re curious about what I was trying to achieve with
this site, I’ve written &lt;a href=&quot;&#x2F;projects&#x2F;this-website&quot;&gt;a whole page&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; about what
I was aiming for and how well I did.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;past-writing&quot;&gt;Past writing&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While this is the first post on this blog, it’s far from the first public
writing I’ve done.  Past highlights include:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>About Me</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 10:41:27 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;about&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;about&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;asside class=&quot;note&quot;&gt;This page is about me, Daniel Sockwell, the person.  If you&#x27;re interested in details about this site, there’s a &lt;a class=&quot;link&quot; href=&quot;..&#x2F;projects&quot;&gt;separate page for that&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.
&lt;&#x2F;asside&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt;  I’m Daniel, and I’m on a mission to bridge the gap between law and technology.  Before embarking on this project, I  was an attorney at a major New York law firm, where my practice focused on civil litigation and emphasised cybersecurity, data privacy, and other intersections between law and technology.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt; 
  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt;I grew up in Birmingham, Alabama, and have also lived in California, Mississippi, New York, North Carolina, and Texas.  When I’m not working on programming or legal topics, you can find me out hiking in the backcountry, reading a science fiction book, or playing a board game with my wife (Race for the Galaxy is a current favorite).
&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>License &amp; Legal</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 10:41:27 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;license&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;license&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt; All non-code content on this site is licensed under the &lt;a class=&quot;link&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;creativecommons.org&#x2F;licenses&#x2F;by&#x2F;4.0&#x2F;legalcode&quot;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. This license generally allows for full duplication of all content, including for commercial use, with attribution.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt; All code contained in this site is licensed under the &lt;a class=&quot;link&quot; href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;opensource.org&#x2F;licenses&#x2F;MIT&quot;&gt;MIT License&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;, which also allows for full duplication of all content, including for commercial use, with attribution.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt; Nothing on this website is legal advice, investment advice, life advice, or any other sort of advice.  This site also does not create an attorney–client relationship or any other sort of relationship.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Home</title>
                <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 08:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;content&#x2F;</link>
                <guid>http:&#x2F;&#x2F;127.0.0.1:1111&#x2F;content&#x2F;</guid>
                <description>  &lt;h1 class=&quot;site-header&quot;&gt; I’m Daniel Sockwell, a web developer who started coding in an odd way:  I was a lawyer in New York, when my firm needed a coding lawyer.&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt;Lawyers and programmers are both incredibly logical, but somehow they don&#x27;t always speak the same language.  My goal is to bridge that gap, by being skilled in both domains—and the first step in doing that is leveling up my programming skills.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt; 
  &lt;p class=&quot;content-p&quot;&gt;As part of that process, I&#x27;ve built this site to provide a home for the &lt;a class=&quot;link&quot; href=&quot;&#x2F;projects&quot;&gt;projects&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; I&#x27;ll build along the way — and to take the opportunity to build a &lt;a href=&quot;&#x2F;projects&#x2F;codesections-website&#x2F;&quot; class=&quot;link&quot;&gt;website that is like Richard Feynman’s radios&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
